export const quesList = [
  {
    question:
      "Workers should receive orders from only one manager”, this principle is termed as",
    options: [
      "Unity of command",
      "Unity of direction",
      "Unity of group",
      "Unity of management",
    ],
    answer: "Unity of command",
  },
  {
    question: "The Hawthorne Experiments are related to",
    options: [
      "Scientific Management",
      "Administrative Management",
      "Human Relations School",
      "Bureaucratic Organization",
    ],
    answer: "Human Relations School",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Managers have long realised that there is no one best way to do things. This statement is suitable for which management approach?",
    options: [
      "Systems Theory",
      "Contingency Theory",
      "Organizational Humanism",
      "Management Science",
    ],
    answer: "Contingency Theory",
  },
  {
    question:
      "g(n) is an upper bound for f(n) that is not asymptotically tight",
    options: ["Big oh", "Big theta", "Big omega", "Amortized"],
    answer: "Big oh",
  },
  {
    question: "Functional foremanship is related to",
    options: [
      "Scientific Management",
      "Administrative Management",
      "Human Relations School",
      "Bureaucratic Organization",
    ],
    answer: "Scientific Management",
  },
  {
    question: "Fayol’s principles are related to",
    options: [
      "Scientific Management",
      "Administrative Management",
      "Human Relations School",
      "Bureaucratic Organization",
    ],
    answer: "Administrative Management",
  },
  {
    question: "X.25 standards covers how many layers?",
    options: ["Two", "Three", "Seven", "Six"],
    answer: "Three",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Working set model for page replacement is based on the assumption of",
    options: [
      "Modularity of references",
      "Working Set Size",
      "Locality of references",
      "Random access",
    ],
    answer: "Locality of references",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Within an organisation, leadership influence will be dependent upon the type of ________ that the leader can exercise over the followers.",
    options: ["knowledge", "power", "delegation", "friendship"],
    answer: "power",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Why, according to stakeholder theory, is it in companies' best interests to pay attention to their stakeholders?",
    options: [
      "If firms only act in their own self-interest, employees may feel exploited.",
      "If firms only act in their own self-interest, the government might put more regulation on them.",
      "If firms only act in their own self-interest, customers might not like the image that the company portrays.",
      "If firms only act in their own self-interest and inflict harm on stakeholders, then society might withdraw its support",
    ],
    answer:
      "If firms only act in their own self-interest and inflict harm on stakeholders, then society might withdraw its support",
  },
  // Continue adding the rest of the questions here in the same format.
];
